(Sheldon:)Stuart, I was wondering
if you could help me find something.
(Stuart:)Happy to, unless it's hope
or a reason to live.
(Sheldon:)Oh, you make me laugh, sad clown.
(Sheldon:)Anyhoo, Leonard will be back
in a couple days
and I need a welcome-home
gift for him.
(Sheldon:)As he's been at sea,
perhaps something
(Sheldon:)with a nautical theme
might be appropriate.
(Stuart:)Okay, well, I don't know
how much you want to spend,
(Stuart:)but I do have this pretty
cool Aquaman statue.
(Sheldon:)Aquaman?
This isn't a gag gift, Stuart.
(Stuart:)Yeah, just as well.
It's a pretty rare piece.
(Stuart:)I'd rather just sell it
to a real collector.
I'm areal collector.
(Sheldon:)How rare is it?
(Stuart:)I shouldn't even have mentioned it.
How about a Batman squirt gun?
(Penny:)Ye--
(Sheldon:)Don't try and trick me
into buying something I don't want.